kialo.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Kialo

September 08, 2017

Please read this privacy policy carefully. It applies to all interactions you have with Kialo’s web services and apps.

## The Information We Collect

_Account Information_. When you create an account with Kialo, we ask you to choose a username and password. We also ask for your email address. You may also choose to provide additional profile information such as a photo, your real name, a short bio, and links to social media accounts.

_Information About Your Use of Kialo_. We receive some information automatically when you use Kialo. This includes data about your device, software, the operating system you use when accessing Kialo, your Internet Protocol address, the date and time of each request you make to Kialo, file types transferred (e.g., photos), and number and size of files transferred.

_Customer Service_. If you file a support ticket, we’ll collect any other personal information you choose to provide us.

_Information About People You Invite to Join a Team or Discussion_. When you invite your friends and colleagues to join a team or discussion on Kialo, we’ll store the email addresses you provide in order to authenticate those users. 

## How We Use Your Information

We use your personal information to keep Kialo running, understand how you use our service, customize your experience, prevent abuse, provide customer support, and improve Kialo. We use your information internally only as needed to accomplish these goals.

## How We Disclose Your Information

We will share your personally identifiable information only in the limited circumstances below. Kialo does not sell your information or share it with third-party advertisers.

_With your permission_. We may share your information with your consent, after letting you know what information will be shared and with whom.

_In response to the law_. We may disclose your information if we believe it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation, or valid legal process. If we are going to release your information, our policy is to provide you with notice unless we are prohibited from doing so by law or court order (e.g., an order under 18 U.S.C. § 2705(b)). We may disclose your information without providing you with prior notice if we believe it’s necessary to prevent imminent and serious bodily harm to a person. Nothing in this policy is intended to limit any legal objections or defenses you might have to demands to compel disclosure of your information, including demands from the government.

_With third parties helping us provide Kialo_. We may share your information with third-party services helping us provide and improve our products. Those third parties access and use your information only on our behalf. The third-party services we use to provide Kialo includes Amazon AWS, Zendesk, Sentry, Google Analytics, Loggly, Slack, PagerDuty, and Postmark. Please note that this Privacy Policy explains Kialo’s practices only, and doesn’t extend to the practices of other services. Take a look at those companies’ privacy policies to learn more about their data practices.

_With other users_. Kialo may display your profile information to other people. We also show public discussions in which you’ve been active by default, but you can choose to hide this timeline. 

_Sale or merger_. If all or part of Kialo is sold, merged, or otherwise transferred to another company in the future, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction. If that happens, Kialo will take reasonable steps to make sure your information continues to be treated consistently with this privacy policy.

We may also disclose aggregate, non-identifying information about how our users use Kialo.

## Web Tracking Policy

_Cookies_. We use cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to identify whether you have logged in and recognize that your web browser has accessed our servers before. 

Most browsers have an option for disabling cookies, but if you disable them you will not be able to log into your Kialo account. 

Some third-party services that we use may place their own identifiers in your browser. This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and not the use of cookies by third parties.

_Local Storage._ Local storage provides similar functionality to cookies, but its contents are kept on your device and not transmitted across the Internet, like cookies are. As with cookies, we use local storage technologies to collect and store information (including personal information) to identify whether you have logged in and recognize that you have accessed Kialo before. 

_Do Not Track_. Some browsers make it possible for you to signal that you don’t want your Internet browsing activity to be tracked. The Internet community hasn’t reached a consensus on how to best honor these signals, so Kialo doesn’t respond to Do Not Track requests at this time.

_Email_. To measure the deliverability of our emails to users, we may embed information in them, such as a web beacon or tag. 

_A special note about Google Analytics_. This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.

In case IP anonymisation is activated on this website, your IP address will be truncated within the area of Member States of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases the whole IP address will be first transferred to a Google server in the USA and truncated there. IP anonymisation is active on this website.

Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing them other services relating to website activity and internet usage.

The IP address that your browser conveys within the scope of Google Analytics will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. You can also opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing the [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) for your current web browser.

## Data Security

Kialo is designed to have several layers of security.

  * We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)/Transport Layer Security (TLS) to create a secure tunnel to protect data in transit between your device and Kialo’s servers.
  * We don’t retain your actual account password, but hash and salt it to help protect it against possible compromise.
  * We narrowly limit the number of Kialo employees who have access to user data through policy and technical access controls.

No transmission over the internet is completely secure, so we can’t absolutely guarantee that unauthorized parties won’t be able to defeat our security measures. You use Kialo at your own risk, and are responsible for taking reasonable measures to secure your account (such as choosing a strong, unique password and keeping it secret).

We are always on the lookout for vulnerabilities in Kialo. If you discover a vulnerability in our service, we would be grateful for your report and encourage you to let us know immediately. If you give us reasonable time to respond to your report before making any information public, and make a good faith effort to avoid privacy violations, destruction of data, and interruption or degradation of our service during your research, we will not pursue any legal action against you or ask law enforcement to investigate your actions.

To report a vulnerability, please email [security@kialo.com](mailto:security@kialo.com).

## Access, Correction and Deletion of Information

If you would like to request access, correction, or deletion of personal information Kialo maintains about you, please email [support@kialo.com](mailto:support@kialo.com).

## Changes to This Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at https://www.kialo.com/privacy. Older versions of the policy will be archived at https://www.kialo.com/privacy/archive. If we make changes that we believe will substantially alter your rights, we will notify you in advance.

## Contact

We would love to hear from you. Kialo welcomes questions, concerns, and feedback about this policy. If you have suggestions for us, let us know at [privacy@kialo.com](mailto:privacy@kialo.com).
